‎（本片根据真实故事改编）
‎（圣阿洛伊修斯医院 ‎ 宾夕法尼亚州 1996年）
‎有人来帮帮忙吗？
Can I get some help in here?
‎第十二病区 紧急情况
Code Blue, section 12.
‎-第十二病区 紧急情况 ‎-这里需要帮助！
Code Blue
I need some help, please!
‎怎么回事？
What's going on?
‎我进来时 发现他在抽搐 ‎然后出现了心脏骤停
Came in, he was seizing, then he started coding.
‎-我去拿诊疗包 ‎-什么情况 查理？
-I'll get the bag. -What's going on, Charlie?
‎我进来时他在抽搐 ‎出现室性心动过速和心脏骤停
I came in, he was seizing, he went into V-tach, and then he coded.
‎-换我来进行按压 ‎-好的
-Let's swap compressions. -Okay.
‎倒数 三 二 一
In three, two, one
‎替换顺利
-Good swap. -Section 12
‎呼吸 二 三 四
Breath, two, three, four
‎说说吧 怎么回事？
Okay, what's going on in here?
‎我在大厅听到了警报声 ‎进来后发现他在抽搐
I heard the alarm from the hall. I came in and saw he was seizing,
‎我关了呼吸机警报 ‎他出现室性心动过速
silenced the vent, noticed he was in V-tach,
‎-接着他就心脏骤停了 ‎-开始按压
and then he went asystolic.
‎注意身后的小推车
-Compressions. -Watch out.
‎尚未注射肾上腺素 ‎按压已持续约一分钟
No epi yet. He's about a minute into compressions.
‎好的 开始注射肾上腺素 ‎一分钟后暂停检查下脉搏
Okay. Let's get the epi started, please,
and let's pause in a minute for a pulse check.
‎收到
Copy that.
‎呼吸
Breath.
‎快速按压
Quick compressions.
‎-12 13 14 15 ‎-呼吸
-12, 13, 14, 15. -Breath.
‎呼吸 2 2 3
-Breath, two. -Two, three.
‎-呼吸 ‎-5 6 7 8 9 10 11
-Breath. -Six, seven, eight, nine, ten
‎暂停 检查下脉搏
Let's pause for a pulse check.
‎14 15 没有脉搏
14, 15. No pulse.
‎-这是可电击复律心律吗？ ‎-是的
-Is that a shockable rhythm? -Yeah, it's shockable.
‎-充电到150焦耳 ‎-充电中
-Uh, let's charge 150 joules. -Charging.
‎-呼吸 ‎-11 12 13 14 15
-Breath. -Ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
‎-快速按压 ‎-快跳动啊
-Quick compressions. -Come on.
‎5 6 7 8 9 10 11
Five, six
-Keeping compressions.
‎-让开 准备使用除颤仪 ‎-都让开了 安全
-Clear for the shock. -You all clear?
‎继续按压胸口 ‎再注射一支肾上腺素
-Clear.
Back on the chest. Let's get another round of epi, please.
‎按压得更深一点
-A little deeper with our compressions. -Breath.
‎呼吸
‎-呼吸 ‎-稳住
Breath. Hold.
‎快速按压
-Keep your compressions. -Talk to me.
‎跟我说句话
‎-快速按压 ‎-呼吸
-Good compressions. -Breath, two, three, four.
‎-呼吸 ‎-13 14 15
-Breath. -13, 14, 15.
‎-呼吸 ‎-能准备一支肾上腺素备用吗？
-Breath. -Can I get an epi standing by?
‎4 5 6 7
Four, five, six, seven
‎-充电 ‎-10 11 12 13
-And charge. -Ten, 11, 12, 13.
‎-好了 都退后 ‎-安全
-All right, let's pull back. -All clear. All is clear.
‎-安全 ‎-安全
-All clear.
‎准备 继续
-Back on.
‎-3 2 1 ‎-呼吸
-Three, two, one -Breath.
‎按压得再快点 拜托了
-Breath. -Faster compressions, please.
‎呼吸
Breath.
‎14 15
14, 15
‎200焦耳
200 joules. Let's hit him.
‎呼吸
Breath.
‎-呼吸 ‎-安全
-Breath.
‎再电击一次
-Hit him again.
‎继续
Back on.
‎呼吸
Breath.
‎-一点反应也没有 ‎-呼吸
-I'm not getting anything. -Breath.
‎10 11 12 13 14 15
Ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
‎-操 ‎-3 4 5
-Fuck. -Three, four, five
‎按压
-Easing compressions. -Eight, nine, ten, 11, 12, 13
‎10 11 12 13
‎好了 他受的苦已经够多了
-All right. -14, 15.
He's had enough.
‎记下死亡时间 给他妻子打电话吧
Mark the time of death.
And let's call his wife.
‎（根据查尔斯格雷伯的 ‎原著《良心护士》改编）
‎（帕克菲尔德纪念医院 ‎新泽西州 2003年）
‎就快好了
-Almost there.
‎-你俩结婚多久了？ ‎-三年
Oh.
-How long have you two been married? -Three years.
‎哇 原来是新婚夫妇啊
Wow. Couple o' newlyweds.
‎宝贝 我好爱你
You know, baby, I love you so much.
‎好了 我这边完事了
All right. I have got it.
‎好的
-All right. -Oh.
‎能给她喝点水吗？
Can we get her some water, please?
‎抱歉 她要到明天才能进食 ‎她可能会噎到的 不过呢
Sorry, she can't have any until tomorrow. She still might choke.
‎这样会让她舒服点的
But here.
This is gonna make her feel better.
‎-我得先走了 但我会回来的 ‎-不 你不能走
-I have to go, but I'll be back. -No. No, you can't go.
‎-你知道规矩的 ‎-不要
You know the rules. I'm not allowed to stay.
‎他们不许我留在这里
Hey, Sam, this chair reclines.
‎山姆 这椅子可以放平
‎你要毯子和枕头吗？
You want a blanket and pillow?
‎好 谢谢 要啊
Yeah. Thanks. Yeah.
‎好的 你不说出去 我也不会说
Okay. I won't tell if you don't.
‎-我马上回来 ‎-谢谢
-I'll be right back. -Thanks.
‎你已经用了那么多药 ‎不知他的血压怎么还这么低
You've pushed a liter. I don't understand why his pressure's low.
‎他们也不知道 ‎但希望半夜再要份检查结果
They don't know, but they want another set of labs at midnight.
‎好吧 那霍莉呢？
Okay, what about Holly?
‎霍莉的情况很稳定 但他们还是得
Holly is stable, but they still need to get--
‎艾米 我得跟你聊聊310病房的病人
Amy.
I'd like to have a word with you about 310.
‎天呐
Jeez.
‎你竟然允许家属在医院过夜？
You let a relative sleep over?
‎没错 是个老人 他很疲惫 ‎当时都凌晨一点了
An old man, yeah. He was exhausted, and it was 1:00 a.m.
‎我们可没有足够的人手 ‎来给家属当酒店
We don't have the staff to run a hotel for relatives.
‎管理层甚至让我 ‎缩减咖啡滤纸的用量
Management has got me rationing coffee filters.
‎每一分钱都卡得很死
Every penny is like a freaking prisoner.
‎我得求琳达加兰才能另外招人
I had to beg Linda Garran for extra staff.
‎好吧
Right.
‎但我给夜班找到帮忙的人了
But I got nights some help, okay?
‎来了个新人 经验丰富 ‎推荐信对他的评价很高
A new guy, tons of experience, great recommendations.
‎哦
-Oh.
‎真棒
Great.
‎不客气
-You're welcome.
‎我是薇薇
-It's Viv.
‎霍莉 我是艾米
Hey, Holly, it's Amy.
‎我来帮你稍微转下方向 ‎把这条手臂放下
All right, I'm just gonna turn you a little bit.
Just put this arm down.
‎我今天刚上班时遇到你妹妹了
Hey, I ran into your sister when I started my shift.
‎她人真好 你们聚得开心吗？
She's so nice. Did you guys have a good time together?
‎真不敢相信她有个双胞胎姐姐
I can't believe she's got twins.
‎我真不知道
I don't know how
‎她是怎么做到的
she does that.
‎好嘞
Okay.
‎一 二 三
One, two, three.
Okay, one
Ah
‎炸鸡好吃吗？用了摇纸袋那招吗？
How was the fried chicken? Did you do the paper bag shake?
‎是的 全都照做了 ‎茱莉亚查尔德教的都做了
Yeah, I did the whole thing. Whatever Julia Child said, I did.
‎棒极了
-Amazing. -Um
‎好像你上周五欠我的钱还没给
Uh, I think you still owe me for last Friday.
‎不过倒也不急
But But it can wait, really.
‎糟糕 对不起
Oh no! I'm sorry.
‎不 真的没关系
No, really, it's okay.
‎我真是个白痴
I'm such an idiot.
‎-我数数 20 40 ‎-你真的不用这样
-Okay, 20, 40 -Listen, you really don't have to do this.
‎-我不需要全部的 ‎-六 七不行的 八 九
-I don't need it all. -Six, seven No, no, no. Eight, nine
‎来 拿着吧 这里是50 真不好意思
Come on. Here, take it. There's 50. Sorry about that.
‎-谢谢 我也挺不好意思 ‎-本来就是你的钱
-Thank you. I'm sorry too. -It's yours.
‎快点 泰迪先生 我们要去上学了
Come on, Mr. Teddy. We're going to school!
‎先前不是说好了 ‎泰迪先生不能去学校的吗？
I think we talked about Mr. Teddy not going to school before.
‎-谢谢 妈妈 ‎-过来 包包先生
-Thanks, Mom. -Come here, Mr. Bag.
‎我准备好了
I'm ready.
‎-再见 妈妈 ‎-再见 祝你今天愉快 我爱你们
-Bye. -Have the best day.
‎-顺便说下 你家没牛奶了 ‎-好的 我会去买的
-Bye! -Love you!
-You need some milk, by the way. -Okay. I'll get it.
‎-回头见 ‎-谢谢
-See you later. -Thanks.
‎去上课了 姑娘们
Off to class, girls.
‎（洛克伦）
Hmm.
‎检查结果不是很理想啊
So it's not the news we were hoping for.
Hmm.
‎有多糟？
How bad we talkin'?
‎如果你继续这样下去
If you continue like this,
‎几个月内 ‎冠状动脉就会出现严重的突发状况
you're looking at a serious coronary incident within months,
‎可能会要了你的命
which could be fatal.
‎上次诊疗时 ‎你提过有不少治疗方案的
At the last appointment, you said that there were options.
‎我知道 ‎但当时我们还没拿到这些检查结果
I know, but that was before we got these results.
‎现在的关键是要尽量拖延时间 ‎让你的心脏能等到那时候
This is now about keeping your heart going long enough.
‎什么时候？
For what?
‎等到能让你进入移植手术名单
To get you on the transplant list.
‎你必须停止工作 请病假吧
And you'll have to stop working, take medical leave.
‎我没办法 我需要医保
I can't. I need health insurance,
‎只有干满一年 我才能有带薪假期
and I don't get paid leave until I've been there a year.
‎你有孩子吧？
You have kids, right?
‎嗯
Mm-hmm.
‎你中风的风险很高
Well, you're at high risk for a stroke.
‎你应该让她们知道你的症状
You should make them aware of the symptoms.
‎发作的早期迹象包括喘不上气 胸闷
The early warning signs of an episode are breathlessness, pressure in the chest,
‎感到虚弱或是眩晕
feeling weak or faint.
‎你必须告诉她们 ‎以防在家里出意外 明白吗？
You need to tell them in case something should happen at home. Okay?
‎-你好 我是洛克伦 ‎-嗯
-Hi. Loughren. -Mm-hmm.
‎我要办结账
I'm checking out.
‎好的
Sure.
‎-你的保险不报这个 对吧？ ‎-对
-So I see you're not covered? -Nope.
‎检查和咨询费总共是980美元
With the test and consultation, it'll be $980.
‎我能用两张卡付吗？
Um
Can I split it in two?
‎没问题
Sure thing.
‎玛丽亚 你能帮我把床摇起来吗？ ‎我要看电视
Maria, can you turn me up? Watch TV.
‎维生素D 谢谢
vitamin D. Thank you.
‎-你好啊 ‎-你好
-Hey. Oh.
‎-你就是新来的吗？ ‎-是的  我叫查理
-You the new guy? Ah, yeah, Charlie.
‎你好 查理 我叫艾米
Hi, Charlie. Amy.
‎-你好 艾米 ‎-很高兴认识你
-Oh, hey, Amy. -Nice to meet you.
‎-欢迎 ‎-谢谢
-Welcome. -Thank you.
‎-有人带你熟悉环境了吗？ ‎-还没有
-Did anyone give you the tour yet? -Uh, no, not yet.
‎我刚才在照顾病人 不过
-I got my patients, but, um -Okay, come on, let me show you around.
‎好吧 那我带你四处转转
The computer's free for all.
‎电脑不固定 随便用的
‎进入洗手间需要密码 这点很重要
There's a code to access the bathroom, very importantly,
‎这个很有创意的密码是4321
the highly original code 4321.
‎无人能破解啊
Uncrackable.
Ha!
‎你用过皮克西自动药品柜吗？
Uh, you ever work with PYXIS?
‎用过 但之前用的好像是1997年款
Yeah, but I think we had the '97 model. The, um
‎好吧 来 我给你演示下
Huh, okay, come on. Let me show you.
‎填上护士证证件号
Put in your nurse ID.
‎然后 输入你的密码
And then your code.
‎输入你需要的药物
You put in what you need.
‎和数量
And the amount.
‎（呋塞米 20毫克药片）
‎拿出来 一 二 三 四 五 再关上抽屉
Take it out. One, two, three, four, five. Close the drawer.
‎-明白了吗？ ‎-是的
-Got it? -Yeah.
‎他们说你经验很丰富 ‎你之前在哪里工作？
Uh, they said you had a lot of experience. Where'd you work at before?
‎我在好多地方工作过
I've been all over, really.
‎-弗洛里安、凡斯、肖兰、圣阿罗 ‎-肖兰
-Florians, Vance, Shawlands, St. Aloysius. -Shawlands.
‎跟我一起培训的女孩就在肖兰工作
A girl I trained with works at Shawlands.
‎-是吗？ ‎-洛丽
-Oh, yeah? -Lori.
‎-洛丽卢卡斯？ ‎-是的
-Lucas? -Yes.
‎我们经常一起共事 ‎她很棒 是个出色的护士
Yeah, we worked together a lot. She's great. She's an amazing nurse.
‎我好久没跟她聊过了 ‎他们还叫她“口袋火箭”吗？
I haven't talked to her forever.
Do they still call her "Pocket Rocket"?
‎没有 我的天 这绰号太好笑了
No. Oh my God. That's hilarious.
‎我要打电话问问她这个
I should I'll call her up and ask her about that.
‎天呐 拜托不要 ‎别告诉她是我跟你说的
Oh God. Please don't. Don't tell her I told you that.
‎你今晚分配到的病人是谁？
Who'd they give you tonight?
‎他们给我分配了谁？
Uh Who did they give me?
‎311号的斯蒂文斯 310号的马丁内斯
I have 311, uh, Stevens. 310, Martinez.
‎你知道他们的名吗？ ‎你们这儿不把名写在门上
Do you know their first names? You guys, you don't put 'em on the doors here.
‎你跟我一模一样 ‎叫名比叫姓要好多了
You're like me. First names are always better.
‎-安娜 我们先从她开始 ‎-安娜
-Ana. Let's start with her. -Ana.
‎她是因为对阿莫西林 ‎有不良反应被送到了急诊科
She presented to the ED with an adverse reaction to amoxicillin.
‎但问题是处方在她的丈夫名下
Kicker is the prescription was her husband's,
‎所以要是我们不帮忙的话 ‎保险公司肯定会让他们吃苦头的
so insurance is gonna try to screw them over
‎-那她皮肤怎么样？ ‎-现在还在脱皮
if we give 'em a chance.
-So how's the skin? -Sloughing off at this point.
‎所以什么意思 只做清洁吗？
And what, so clears only?
‎对 今晚第一位病人 ‎来吧 我带你去见她
Yeah. First sip tonight. Come on. I'll introduce you.
‎待会儿就能喝水了
Water later.
‎嘿 如胶似漆的小情侣
Well, hey there, lovebirds.
‎-看我带谁来了 ‎-你好
-Look what I brought. -Hey.
‎来
Here you go.
‎这是不是你尝过最美味的东西？
Mm!
Is that the best thing you have ever tasted?
‎嗯
-Yeah. -Mm-hmm?
‎来
-There you go.
‎你知道吗？我们慢慢来 好吗？
You know what? Let's start slow, all right?
‎-我给你介绍一下查理 ‎-你好
-I wanna introduce you to Charlie. -Hey.
‎今晚他是你的护士 ‎如果需要我的话 我就在附近
He's gonna be your nurse this evening, but, you know, I'm around if you need me.
‎知道了吗？
Okay?
‎-山姆 你怎么样？还好吧？ ‎-喝够了就告诉我
-So -How you doing, Sam? Good?
You let me know when you've had enough.
‎-感觉疼吗？疼？好的 ‎-我待会儿再来
Mm.
-Okay, is it burning? It burns? Okay. -I'll check in in a bit.
‎我们先歇一下 好吗？
Well, let's take a pause, okay?
‎听说你这几天很难受 是吗？
So, um tell me, I heard you had a rough couple of days. Yeah?
‎有需要的话 就按按钮
Well, you guys just push on the button if you need anything.
‎我随时都在 今晚我就是你的艾米
Anytime, I'm here. I'm your Amy for tonight.
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿
-Hey.
‎我的病人都安顿好了 ‎准备去餐厅吃点东西
Hey.
Uh, so mine are all settled,
so I was just gonna go to the cafeteria, grab some food.
‎-你想要些什么吗？ ‎-抱歉 食堂十一点就关门了
-You want something? -Sorry. Cafeteria closes at 11:00.
‎-我该早点告诉你的 ‎-哎呀 没关系 我也没那么饿
-I should've told you that. -Oh shit. No problem. I'm not that hungry.
‎-抱歉 ‎-不 我去自动贩卖机买点就行了
-Sorry. -No. I'll hit up the vending machines.
‎嘿 你喜欢吃鸡蛋吗？
-Hey, you know what? You like eggs? -Uh
‎我有很大一份可能坏了的鸡蛋沙拉 ‎我宁愿跟人分着吃
I have a large questionable egg salad that I'd prefer to share.
‎-你懂的 要死一起死嘛 ‎-不用了 谢谢你
-You know, safety in numbers. -I'm fine, thank you.
‎不 等我处理完霍莉就带过去找你
No, no. I'll bring it to the desk when I'm finished with Holly here.
‎-你确定吗？ ‎-嗯
-You sure? -Yeah.
‎好吧 谢谢
'Kay, thanks.
‎里头的面包丁很好吃
I like the croutons.
‎-你是说这软趴趴的饼干吗？ ‎-原来是饼干吗？
-Mm, you mean the soggy crackers? -That's what they are?
‎这才是沙拉的精髓
That's the real delicacy of the salad.
‎是啊 我大女儿做的
Yeah. My eldest daughter made it.
‎我们家不会做饭的女人代代相传
She comes from a long line of women who can't cook.
‎怎么 平常是你老公做饭？
What, so your husband cooks?
‎不 我们家只有我和我女儿
No, it's just me and my girls.
‎我有两个女儿
Oh. I have two girls.
‎一个四岁 一个七岁
Uh Four and seven.
‎我家一个五岁 一个九岁
Mine are five and nine.
‎-哦 是吗？ ‎-嗯
-Oh, yeah? -Mm-hmm.
‎我没跟孩子住一起了 孩子妈搬走了 ‎过去要六个小时 所以
I don't live with mine anymore though. Their mom moved, like, six hours away, so
‎这也是我来这里的原因
That's kinda why I'm here.
‎我觉得这个很好吃
-Well, I think this is great.
‎好吧
-Okay.
‎-哦他是对 ‎-307房的
-Oh, he's-- 307.
‎史蒂文 他还有一分钟就要尿了
Yep. Steven. I have about one minute before he pees.
‎我来吧
I got it.
‎你确定吗？谢谢
You sure? Thanks.
‎嘿 史蒂文 我是查理 ‎艾米现在有点忙 所以
Hey, Steven. I'm Charlie. I'm afraid Amy's busy right now, so
‎我能帮上什么？出了什么问题？
Can I help? A little problem?
‎查理 你好吗？
‎不 可以这样的！
Yes, you can!
‎-你瞧 ‎-那又怎样？你又不喜欢她
-Look. -So what? You don't even like her.
‎-我喜欢！她是我的朋友 洁姬 ‎-没人会注意到的
-I do! She's my friend, Jackie! -Nobody's gonna notice that.
‎大家都会注意到的
Everybody's gonna notice!
‎不 不会的 别这样 真的
No, they're not. Come on. Really.
‎他们会的！
Yes, they are! I don't know why I have to keep using these.
‎-为什么我总得用这些东西 ‎-嘿
Hey.
‎-破烂东西！ ‎-什么？
It's such crap!
‎-停下来！怎么回事？ ‎-你毁了我的鞋子！
-Stop it! What's going on here? -You ruined my shoes!
‎我没有！我只是想帮你
I did not! I tried to help you.
‎-你介意去和玛雅坐一会儿吗？ ‎-显然不是 洁姬
-Would you mind sitting with Maya? -No, you obviously didn't, Jackie!
‎-她在 ‎-没事
-She's in the-- -That's okay.
‎你干吗对着洁姬大喊大叫？
Why the hell are you yelling at Jackie?
‎-她把鞋底粘回去了 ‎-这有什么大不了的 亚历克斯
-She glued the bottom back on. -It's not a big deal, Alex.
‎-我可以帮你刮掉 ‎-是你让她这么做的
-I can scrape it off. -You told her to.
‎你瞧 一刮就掉
Look, it comes right off.
‎-但两只鞋上都有 ‎-看到了吗？我可以弄掉
-But it's on both shoes. -See? I can take it off.
‎-我 ‎-不 你弄不掉
-I'll just-- -No, you can't.
‎冷静点 又不是世界末日
Calm down. It's not the end of the world.
‎不
No.
‎-等等 听我说 我知道 ‎-别说了
-Wait. Hey, hey, hey, hey! Listen. I know. -Stop--
‎我在努力 我知道你不像你的朋友们 ‎有那么多东西 但我已经在努
I'm trying, okay? I know you don't have as much as your friends, but I'm try--
‎我什么东西都没有！
I don't get anything!
‎-连你都不在我身边 ‎-对不起
-I don't even get to have you. -I'm sorr
‎真要命
Oh fuck.
‎艾米？
Amy?
‎怎么回事？你没事吧？
What's going on? You okay?
‎我没事
I'm fine.
‎好吧 我就坐这儿陪你 ‎等你好起来 好吗？
Okay, well, I'll just sit here until you feel better, okay?
‎和我一起深呼吸
Now breathe with me.
‎继续呼吸
Keep breathing.
‎没事的
It's okay.
‎心肌症
Cardiomyopathy.
‎我的心脏上有血疱
Blood blisters on on my heart.
‎好吧 那你为什么还要工作？
Okay. So why are you working?
‎我没有医疗保险
I don't have health insurance.
‎那我们院呢？
What about here?
‎-和心脏病医生谈过了吗？ ‎-不 求你了
-Did you speak to a cardiologist? -No, please.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎别告诉他们
Don't tell them.
‎-我会被开除的 ‎-好吧
-I'll get fired. -Okay.
‎我不会告诉任何人的
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
‎-好 ‎-嗯
-Okay. -Yeah.
‎你还要工作多久才会有保险？
How much longer do you need to work here before you get your insurance?
‎四个月
Four months.
‎好的
Okay.
‎我会帮你的
I can help you.
‎加油
Come on.
‎你能坚持四个月的
You can do four months.
‎不会有事的
You're gonna be okay.
‎好吗？
Yeah?
‎-你冷吗？ ‎-嗯
-Are you cold? -Mm-hmm.
‎来
Here.
‎-这个门出问题了 ‎-是这个
-Something's wrong with the door. -Oh, it's this.
‎谢谢
Ah. Thanks.
‎-今晚会很漫长啊 ‎-说到有精力 公园怎么样？
-It's gonna be a long night. -Speaking of energy, how was the park?
‎她取消了
-She canceled. -No!
‎-不 哦 抱歉 ‎-对 改到下周了
-Yeah. Moved it to next week. -Oh, that's hard.
‎打电话过来时我正要去接孩子
Called just as I was about to pick up the girls.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎说实话这在我意料之中
Kind of expected it, to be honest.
‎等等
Uh, one sec.
‎嘿 怎么了？索雅在哪？
Hey, what's up? Where's Sonya?
‎什么情况？
What have we got?
‎她家里有点事 我想和她交接一下
She had a family thing, so I said I'd do her handover.
‎-310 ‎-是的
-Uh, 310 -Yeah.
‎刚换班人就去世了
expired right at shift change.
‎-安娜？ ‎-马丁内斯夫人
-Ana? -Yes. Mrs. Martinez.
‎别问 我也不知道是什么情况
Don't ask. I don't know what happened.
‎给丈夫打过电话了 他在来的路上
The husband was called. He's on his way.
‎309房间 中午左右情况恶化
309, he went sideways at around noon
‎安娜死了
Ana died.
‎应该是八点左右 ‎呼吸科来给他上了管
Should be up around eight. Respiratory came up. They tubed him
‎他们怎么能就这样把她撂在这儿？
How could they just leave her like this?
‎我妈就是在医院去世的 ‎那时候我还很小
My mom died in a hospital when I was a kid.
‎等我去医院看她时
When I got there to see her, it was
‎首先 他们把遗体弄丢了
Well, first of all, they lost the body.
‎-不会吧 ‎-很荒谬吧 丢了几个小时
-No. -Yeah. Insane. Just for a couple of hours.
‎后来他们找到她时
But, you know, and then when they did find her, it was this.
‎她身上都没穿齐 裸着体 乱七八糟的
She was, like, you know, half uncovered, naked Total mess.
‎之后很长一段时间 ‎我一想到她 她就是那个样子
For the longest time, that was the memory. That was how I thought of her.
‎天哪 查理
Oh, Charlie.
‎所以对我来说 这件事很重要
So, for me, this is the important part.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎保留点尊严
Find some dignity.
‎马丁内斯先生在外面
Mr. Martinez is out there.
‎他很想跟你谈谈 艾米
He would really like to speak with you, Amy.
‎去吧
Go.
‎-你可以吗？ ‎-放心吧 交给我
-You good? -Yeah, I got this.
‎好吧 再跟我说说情况
All right, so give me the story again.
‎好嘞 是这样的 马丁内斯夫人 ‎也就是安娜 离奇死亡
All right, let me see. Suspicious death of Mrs. Martinez, Ana.
‎因为对阿莫西林有不良反应 ‎被送到了急诊室
Presented to the emergency room with adverse reaction to amoxicillin.
‎好吧 那又如何？ ‎对抗生素过敏 还有别的吗？
All right, so? Reacts to some antibiotic. What else?
‎他们不确定
They're not sure.
‎-他们不知道死因吗？ ‎-不知道
-They don't know what killed her? -No.
‎她多大年纪？
How old was she?
‎77岁
Seventy-seven.
‎那我们为什么要来这里？
So why are we here?
‎会议室在这边
The conference room's right this way.
‎警探们 布劳恩 鲍德温 欢迎
Detectives, Braun, Baldwin, welcome.
‎我是琳达加兰 风险经理
I'm Linda Garran, risk manager.
‎这位是邓肯贝蒂律师
This is Duncan Beattie, attorney.
‎我们的董事会
Our board.
‎你们可能认识马尔科姆伯雷尔 ‎他是市议会的人
You two might know Malcolm Burrel from the City Council.
‎我非常支持当地警方和地方检察官
I am a huge supporter of the local force and the district attorney.
‎很高兴见到各位
Ah, well, nice to meet you all.
‎好吧 我们知道的不多
Okay, well, we don't know much.
‎只知道有一个人死了
Just that there's been a death.
‎病人死亡的原因无法解释
An unexplainable incident in which the patient expired.
‎好的 怎么无法解释了？
Okay. Unexplainable how?
‎医学专家的意见是
Well, it's the opinion of the medical experts
‎这种药物不良反应十分不寻常
that this was an unusual adverse reaction to medications.
‎但我们完全没发现任何迹象 ‎表明这是人为的
But we found absolutely nothing to suggest this was intentional.
‎为什么找我们？
Then why call us?
‎我们没觉得需要警方介入
We didn't think this was a police matter,
‎但卫生署规定我们必须联系你们
but the Department of Health dictates when we should reach out,
‎于是我们就照做了
and here we are.
‎用了哪些药物？
What are the medications?
‎都列出来了
Um Well, all are listed.
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎这文件挺复杂的
It's quite a complicated document.
‎我试试看吧
I'll take my chances.
‎如果你翻到第三页
Well, if you if you turn to the third page,
‎就能看见病患一 ‎实验室结果异常的区间
you can see the window in which patient 1 had abnormal laboratory results
‎以及危及生命的症状
and life-threatening symptoms.
‎马丁内斯太太的尸体呢？
Where's Mrs. Martinez's body?
‎已经交给家属了
Uh, released to the family.
‎他们准备打官司？
They put a lawsuit together?
‎我们觉得家属并不知道
We don't believe that the family are aware
‎病患一的死亡不寻常
of the unusual circumstances around patient 1's expiration.
‎你们不应该告诉他们吗？
Isn't that something you should've disclosed to them?
‎我们当时也不知道
It was an evolving situation.
‎帕克菲尔德正当地咨询了法律顾问
Parkfield rightly sought legal counsel
‎确保一切正规合法
to make sure everything was done correctly.
‎好吧 但马丁内斯太太的尸体在哪？ ‎我们怎样才能拿到？
Okay, but Mrs. Martinez's body is where? How do we get it?
‎据我们所知 家属已经将她火化
It's our understanding the family have cremated her.
‎她什么时候死亡的？
When did she die?
‎七周前
Seven weeks ago.
‎我们那时在进行内部调查
We were conducting an internal investigation.
‎所以才通知晚了
Hence the lag.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎当然了 我们必须要询问一下 ‎重症监护室的所有员工
Well, of course we'll need to interview all the staff that works in the ICU.
‎让开 让开 我是市里的重要人物
Make way, make way. I am an important person of the town.
‎事实上 我是全市最重要的人
In fact, I am the most important person of the town,
‎甚至可能是贝克斯县西部最重要的人
if not the most important person west of the Pecos.
‎“根本没听过那地方”
"Wherever that is!"
‎我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长
I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls.
‎“那你是做什么的？”
"So, what do you do?"
‎“做什么”？什么都不做 我是镇长
"Do"? I don't do anything. I'm the mayor.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎“你现在该做点什么了”
"Well, you have to do something now."
‎“虽然这里只是个不知名的偏僻小镇
"This may be just a one-horse town without the horse,
‎但现在被外星人入侵了”
but it's been invaded by aliens."
‎我得去查一下我的书《如何当镇长》
I'll have to look it up in my book of How to be Mayor.
‎首先 可以戴上漂亮的项链
One. You get to wear a fancy chain.
‎其次 你有专属司机 ‎开着大车带着你到处兜风
Two. You get driven around in a big car by your very own chauffeur.
‎第三
Three
‎“还可以吃” 这里
Om nom!
You eat. It's
‎“三是可以免费吃喝”
"Three. You eat and drink for fr--"
‎-我永远也不可能拿到这个角色了 ‎-别灰心
-I'm never gonna get this part! -Don't get frustrated, honey.
‎开玩笑? 现在已经很好了
Are you kidding? This is great, Alex.
‎不 老师说我 应该穿西装留胡子
No, and the teacher said that I should wear a suit and have a mustache.
‎因为我是镇长 所以要打扮成男人 ‎他说女镇长会很奇怪
Dress like a man because I'm the mayor. He said a girl mayor would be weird.
‎但女人可以当镇长
Women can be mayors.
‎我跟他说了 但
I told him that, but--
‎这个戏讲的是外星人入侵 ‎有个女镇长倒是最奇怪的部分了？
It's a play about an alien invasion, and the female mayor's the weird part?
‎让那家伙去死
-Screw that guy.
‎-我来了！ ‎-嘿！
-I'm here! -Hey!
‎-洁姬！ ‎-不！你还不能走
-Jackie! -No! You can't go yet.
‎抱歉 孩子
-Oh, sorry, kiddo. -Come on, sweetheart.
‎-来吧 亲爱的 猜猜我有什么 ‎-来
-Come here. -Guess what I brought you.
‎-猜猜我给你带了什么 ‎-糖吗？
‎好 抓着我的手
Okay, take my hands.
‎跟着我说
Repeat after me.
‎我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长
I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls.
‎我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的市长
‎我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长
I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls.
‎-我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长 ‎-我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长
-I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls. -I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls.
‎我是哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长 ‎你可以的
I am the mayor of Humdrum Falls.
You got this.
‎一份奶 两份糖
Cream and two sugars.
‎他们把内部调查报告送过来了没？
They send over that internal investigation yet?
‎还没有 他们说还需要时间 ‎整理所有相关文件
Oh, not yet. They say they need more time to compile all the relevant files.
‎七个星期还不够吗？
Seven weeks wasn't enough of a head start?
‎可不是嘛
You'd think.
‎你想让我去
You want me to
‎调查一下员工吗？
go through the staff?
‎已经调查完了
Already did.
‎有一名护士在宾州被控非法入侵罪名
One of the nurses had a criminal trespass charge
over in Pennsylvania.
‎是吗？是名护士？
Oh yeah? A nurse?
‎是的 是名男护士 叫查尔斯卡伦
Yeah, a male nurse. Charles Cullen. C-U-L-L-E-N.
‎噢 什么时候的事？
Huh. When?
‎八年前
Uh, eight years ago.
‎-宾州哪个区？ ‎-帕尔默
-What district was it in Pennsylvania? -Palmer.
‎-帕尔默警察局 ‎-你好 女士
-Palmer Police Department. Hello, ma'am.
‎我是新泽西州检察官办公室 ‎凶案组的布劳恩警探
I'm Detective Braun with Homicide in the Prosecutor's Office in New Jersey.
‎你们在1995年抓过一个人 ‎我需要他的一些背景信息
I need some background on a guy you picked up there in '95.
‎可以帮我查一下档案吗？
Could you pull the case jacket for me?
‎-可以提供名字吗？ ‎-查尔斯卡伦
-Do you have a name for me? -It's Charles Cullen.
‎-噢 档案上有张便利贴 ‎-档案上有张便利贴
-Oh, there's a Post-it note on the file. There's a Post-it note on the file.
‎她不确定是该不该出现在档案上 ‎可以读一下吗？
She's not sure if it's supposed to be there. Can you spell that?
‎上面写着“地高辛”
It says "digoxin."
‎地高辛？是什么？是药还是什么？
Digoxin? What is that? A medicine or something?
‎还有其他相关信息吗？
Uh, you got anything else on him?
‎因非法入侵被捕
Picked up for trespassing and
‎1995年因非法入侵和骚扰被捕
Okay. Picked up for trespassing and harassment in '95.
‎据说他和同事分手后 ‎还把她的轮胎给划了
Says he slashed a coworker's tires after they broke up.
‎指控撤销了
The charges were dropped.
‎-怎么回事？指控撤销了？ ‎-是的 所有指控
-What's that? -Yep, all charges.
‎-对 ‎-哦
Charges were dropped?
-Yeah. -Oh.
‎好的 非常感谢
Okay, thanks so much.
‎-好的 ‎-再见
-Yep. -Bye-bye.
‎有点不对劲
Something's not right.
‎帕克菲尔德等了将近两个月才上报
Parkfield waited almost two months to report it.
‎不想分享内部调查情况
Internal investigation you don't wanna share.
‎请高价律师
Expensive lawyers.
‎好
Okay.
‎那么
Well
‎他们有什么理由要掩盖一起死亡呢？
What possible reason could they have for covering up a death?
‎对吧？有什么动机？
Right? What are the motives?
‎这是门生意
It's a business. There's never a better motivation than money
‎这种破事没什么比赚钱更大的动机了
when it comes to that shit, right?
‎喂？大家可以继续吃饭
Hello? You can keep eating.
‎不会耽误大家太久的
We won't take up too much of your time.
‎只是想让大家知道 ‎医院正在调查一个事情
We just wanna make you aware of an event the hospital is looking into.
‎同时想向各位保证董事会和我
We wanted to assure you all that the board and I
‎正在处理这件事及与其相关的一切
are dealing with the incident and everything connected to it.
‎但我们觉得最好 ‎还是要把大家召集起来
But we thought it best to bring you all together,
‎让大家都知道警方也参与进来了
make everyone universally aware that the police are also involved.
‎-还有 ‎-关于什么事啊？
-And that-- -What is this about?
‎重症监护室出现了 ‎一例病人死亡的情况
Uh, there's been an issue with a patient's death in the ICU.
‎死因很可疑吗？ ‎毕竟如果警方在调查的话
Was the death suspicious? I mean, if the police are investigating
‎我想澄清一下 是我们在调查 ‎当地警方只是在协助
I wanna be clear. We are investigating with the assistance of the local police.
‎-你知道他们在说哪个病人吗？ ‎-不
-Do you know which patient? -No.
‎但是由于牵涉到外部调查
But due to the fact that outside investigation is involved,
‎我们的律师贝蒂先生在这里
uh, Mr. Beattie, our attorney, is here,
‎想跟大家说几句
and he would like to say something as well.
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎我只想说一下 ‎我之后会找各位单独面谈
Yes, uh, I just wanna say
that I'll be discussing with each of you individually,
‎但也要对所有人做个笼统的声明
but as a blanket statement to all,
‎我只想说 在这种情况下
I just wanna say that in times like this,
‎患者的隐私绝对是头等大事
patient confidentiality has to be an absolute priority.
‎你们每个人的合同里 ‎在这方面已经写的很明白了
Your individual contracts are very precise when it comes to this.
‎任何人在与警方交谈时
Anyone speaking to the police
‎如果没有医院代表在场
without a representative of the hospital present
‎都是违约行为
would be in breach of their contract.
‎因此 总而言之 ‎我和贝蒂先生是来帮助你们的
So at the end of the day, Mr. Beattie and I are here for you.
‎你们在接受任何问询时 ‎我们都希望在场
Uh, we wanna be present for any interviews,
‎因为我们会你们争取最大的权益
because we have your best interests at heart.
‎你们随便问 但必须让她待在房间里
You have full access, but she's gotta be in the room.
‎不 绝对不行 她不能进去
No. Absolutely not. She can't be in there.
‎她是风险经理 陪同面谈是她的职责
That lady's the risk manager. It's her job to be in there.
‎老板就坐在旁边 谁敢如实回答啊？
Who's gonna talk if their boss is in the interview?
‎我们甚至都不知道发生了什么 ‎连尸体都没有
We don't even know what happened. We don't even have a body.
‎他们唯一的条件是她要在房间里
The only condition that they asked for is that she be in the room
‎还有你们不能问用药的具体情况
and that you don't talk specific about medications.
‎我明白这是他们的要求 ‎可你为什么要答应呢？
I understand them asking for it, but why did you give it to them?
‎你不应该是检察官吗？
You're supposed to be the prosecutor.
‎据我所知
As far as I can see,
‎他们正在全力配合你们的调查
they're cooperating fully with your investigation.
‎我们就只有这些 这也叫配合？
This is all we have. Is this cooperation?
‎他们跟我说过了
They told me about that.
‎他们正在整理文件 ‎一整理完就会发过来
They're getting the documents together. It's done. They're sending it first thing.
‎那我问问你
Let me ask.
‎如果真没问题的话 ‎为什么帕克菲尔德要搞内部调查
Why would Parkfield conduct an internal investigation,
‎整整七周的内部调查
a seven-week internal investigation,
‎然后才通知我们 ‎而且还要求让她参与审讯？
then call us in and put her in the room if it was nothing?
‎尽职调查
Due diligence.
‎就这么说定了 让她在场
I'm shutting it down. She's in the room.
‎就这样了
Done.
‎嗨 艾米
Hi, Amy.
‎嗨
Hi.
‎洛克伦护士
Nurse Loughren.
‎-这位是布劳恩警官 鲍德温 ‎-你好吗？
-This is Officer Braun, Baldwin. -How you doin'?
‎-有什么事吗？ ‎-问几个非正式的问题而已
-What is this about? -Just some informal questions.
‎警官们要和重症监护室的 ‎一些员工了解下情况
The officers are speaking to a number of staff in the ICU.
‎好的
Okay.
‎你还记得安娜马丁内斯吗？
Do you remember Ana Martinez?
‎记得 安娜是我的病人
Yeah, Ana was my patient.
‎你记得她发生过什么奇怪的事吗？
Do you recall anything odd about what happened to her?
‎奇怪？
Odd?
‎嗯 她去世了
Well, she died.
‎是的 非常让人难受 很突然
Yeah, and it was very sad. It was sudden.
‎突然？
Sudden?
‎病人是在重症监护室去世的 但
Well, patients die in the ICU, but
‎我们没想到会这样
we didn't expect it.
‎抱歉打扰 我能和你谈谈吗？
I don't mean to interrupt. Can I see you for a minute?
‎不好意思 我马上回来
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
‎最好是重要的事 我现在不想被打扰
This better be important. I wanted no interruptions.
‎你觉得有什么不对劲吗？
You see any deviations there?
‎没有
Mm-mm.
‎等等 对了 她的血糖
Wait, yeah. Her glucose.
‎是
It's, uh
‎对了 血糖有问题
Yeah, the blood sugars, it's wrong.
‎缺少C肽
Uh, there's no C-peps.
‎-很奇怪 ‎-那是什么意思？
-That's weird. -What does that mean?
‎这说明她体内的胰岛素 ‎并不是在她体内合成的
Uh, it means that the insulin in her system wasn't made in her body.
‎是有人注射进去的
Someone gave it to her.
‎从这点你就能判断 ‎有人给她注射了胰岛素？
So you can tell from that that she was given insulin?
‎这个嘛 药单上没有 ‎而且她没有糖尿病
Well, it's not on the list, and, you know, she's, uh not diabetic,
‎所以胰岛素可能是双重用药差错
so the insulin would've been a double medication error,
‎这很罕见 所以
which is really rare, so
‎双重用药差错？很少见吗？
A double medication error? It's rare?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎-那会不会害死她？ ‎-肯定会
-Would that have killed her? -Sure.
‎抱歉
Sorry.
‎我们说到哪了？
-Where were we?
‎我看看 哦
Uh, let's see. Oh.
‎可以跟我们聊聊你的同事吗？
Can you tell us anything about your coworkers?
‎你不介意 ‎她回答和同事相关的问题吧？
You don't mind if she answers a question about a colleague, do you, Ms. Garran?
‎-当然不介意 ‎-很好
-Of course not. -Good
‎我们知道你和查理卡伦一起工作
We understand that you work with a Charlie Cullen.
‎-是的 ‎-他会不会跟这事有关？
-Yeah. -Could he be involved in this?
‎我觉得你的结论太草率了 警官
I think you're jumping to conclusions there, Officer.
‎查理当时不在场
Charlie wasn't there.
‎安娜是白班去世的 ‎查理和我都上夜班
I mean, Ana died on the day shift. Charlie and I both work nights.
‎我们没有怀疑的理由 ‎这只不过是一场意外
We have no reasons to suspect it was anything other than an accident.
‎谢谢你 艾米
Thank you, Amy.
‎我很了解查理
I know Charlie really well.
‎我们每次都一起轮班 ‎他是个很优秀的护士
We work every shift together, and he's a very good nurse.
‎-他是不会犯这种错的 ‎-谢谢你 艾米
He wouldn't have made a mistake like that.
Thank you, Amy.
‎-对了 内部调查报告在哪里？ ‎-我们还在核对所有的信息
-So where's that internal investigation? -We're still reviewing everything.
‎你们不用核对了 就这样给我们吧
Well, we don't need you to review it. We'll just take it as it is.
‎那我通知团队明天把箱子寄给你们
I'll instruct the team to send you the boxes tomorrow.
‎但我希望你们推断出来 ‎这七周过得非常不容易
But I hope you can deduce that, um it's been a tough seven weeks.
‎是八周
Eight.
‎已经八周了
It's been eight weeks.
‎杰克艾文斯 1988年7月19日出生
- Jack Ivins. July 19, '88.
‎周四做完胆囊手术 没有出现并发症
Recovering from gallbladder surgery on Thursday. There was no complications.
‎线接进来了
Line in.
‎准备再次电击 150焦耳
Gonna need you to get ready to do another shock, 150 joules.
‎-大家都准备好了 ‎-你 我都准备好了
-Everybody clear. -Clear.
‎-氧气也没问题 ‎-传送电击 电击
Deliver the shock. Shock.
‎恢复按压
Resume compressions.
‎1 2 3  4 5 6
One and two and three and four and five and six
‎按压
-Compressions. -Nine, ten, 11, 12, 13
‎9 10 11 12 13
‎停止按压 看看心跳的情况
Hold compressions. Let's check for a rhythm.
‎-我这边什么都没有 ‎-坚持除颤 继续按压
-I got nothing. -Persistent V-fib.
Resume compressions.
‎先注射一毫克肾上腺素
Let's get one milligram of epinephrine IV started.
‎6 7 8 9 10
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten
‎准备再次电击 200焦耳
Let's get prepared to give it another shock, 200 joules.
‎肾上腺素准备好了
Epi ready. In line.
‎继续呼吸
Continue your breathing.
‎-20 ‎-继续按压
-Twenty. -Keep your compressions.
‎跟我说句话
Talk to me.
‎肾上腺素准备好了吗？
-Is that epi ready?
‎交换 5 4 3 2
Swap in, five, four, three, two
‎35
-You're all clear.
‎你们都准备好了
-Oxygen's clear.
‎氧气没问题
‎我进来了 脉搏微弱
I'm moving in. Low pulse, low pulse.
‎可恶 还是没压力
-Shit, no pressure, still.
‎4 5  6 7 8 9 10
Four and five and six and seven
and eight and nine, ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
‎11 12 13 14 15
‎该死
Shit.
‎25 赶紧！
Twenty-five. Now! Now!
‎快点！
Let's go!
‎（密码）
‎（请去掉：一片 取消）
‎吃吧
Take these.
‎你会被开除的
You'll get fired.
‎皮克西自动药品柜有个故障
So there's a fault in the PYXIS.
‎如果你晚点取消 抽屉还是会开的
So if you cancel a request late enough, it opens anyway.
‎那是是偷药 查理
That's stealing meds, Charlie.
‎艾米 别这样 不要担心 ‎我会帮你渡过难关的
Amy, stop. Now, please don't worry. I'm gonna help you get through this.
Okay, thank you.
‎他怎么说？
Hey, what did he say?
‎我赞同他的想法
I think he's right. I think you probably do need to tell Alex,
‎我觉得你应该告诉告诉亚历克斯
‎以防我不在的时候有什么事情
just in case something happens and I'm not there.
‎她们现在除了我谁都没有了 ‎我不能丢下她们
They don't have anyone but me. I can't leave them.
‎不 你不会丢下她们的 艾米
No, you're not leaving them, Amy.
‎不会发生这种事情的 ‎还要多久？两个月？
That's not happening. It's What is it? Two months?
‎我会帮你的 你会顺利做完手术 ‎继续跟你女儿们在一起
Okay, so I'm gonna help you do this.
Get your surgery, be with your girls. That's what's happening.
‎一定会这样的
‎好吗？
Okay?
‎但我觉得你应该告诉亚历克斯
But I think you should tell Alex.
‎我知道这听着很吓人 但其实不是
I know it sounds scary, but it really isn't.
‎每个人的心脏都有心室
Everybody's hearts have these ventricles.
‎-就是一种空隙 ‎-对
-They're just these spaces. -Yeah.
‎是两个气球一样的小空隙 ‎里面充满了血液
They're two little spaces like balloons that fill with blood.
‎-它们把血液输送到全身 ‎-嗯
-They move the blood around the body. -Mm-hmm.
‎不过 我的心室
And um mine, they just, you know,
‎太大了 而且还有点薄
they're too big, and they just got a little thin.
‎但我不会有事的 我有吃药
But I am gonna be okay. I've got medication.
‎有医生在照顾我 很快就会恢复正常
I have doctors taking care of me, and I'm gonna feel normal soon.
‎但你妈妈需要我们帮忙 亚历克斯
But your mom's gonna need our help, Alex.
‎如果她跌倒了 或者说话很奇怪
If she were to fall or, um, you know, start speaking funny,
‎或者很难把她叫醒 或者其他情况
or you struggle to wake her or something,
‎你就你把玛雅放在电视前面 ‎接着打911 然后给我打电话
then you just you put Maya in front of the TV,
you call 911, and then you call me.
‎但是不会出现这种情况 不会出现的
Yeah, but that's not gonna happen. It's not gonna happen.
‎一切都会好起来的 我不会有事的
Everything's gonna be fine. I'm gonna be okay.
‎我可以去看电视吗？
Can I just go watch some TV?
‎好的
Okay.
‎我就在这里 如果你想
But I'll be here if you wanna
‎查尔斯卡伦
Charles Cullen with a C.
‎卡伦
C-U-L-L-E-N.
‎好的 请稍等 正在找他的记录
Sure. Give me a second while I pull up his records.
‎太好了 谢谢
Great, thanks.
‎好的 我先和我老板确认一下
Okay, I just need to check something with my boss.
‎好的 没问题
Okay. Sure.
‎喂？
Hello?
‎喂 我是布劳恩警探 请问您是？
Hello. Detective Braun here. Uh, who am I talking to?
‎马克罗西 ‎圣阿洛伊修斯医院集团的律师
Mark Rossi. Attorney for St. Aloysius Hospital Group.
‎罗西先生 你好 我希望你可以帮帮忙
Mr. Rossi, hi. I'm hoping you can help me out.
‎我正在你们之前一位员工的信息
I'm looking for some information on one of your former employees
‎查尔斯卡伦 是在1996年
from back in '96, Charles Cullen.
‎我们的员工资料都是严格保密的
Our employee data is treated with strict confidentiality.
‎我只是想确认一下他的工作日期而已
I'm just looking to confirm his dates of employment, not much more than that.
‎如果收到你的传票
We'd be happy to release any relevant information
‎我们会很乐意公布相关信息
as soon as we see your subpoena.
‎好的 非常感谢
Okay, yep, thank you so much.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎这他妈的是在搞笑吧
This is a fucking joke.
‎每次提到他的名字 ‎没人透露任何信息
Whenever they hear his name, no one wants to say anything.
‎鲍德温警探？
Detective Baldwin?
‎-对 ‎-帕克菲尔德纪念医院寄来的
-Yeah. -It's from Parkfield Memorial Hospital.
‎这是内部调查资料
It's the internal investigation.
‎-你只用在这里签字就好 ‎-好吧
-Just need you to sign here. -All right.
‎-需要帮忙搬箱子吗？ ‎-不用 就这么点东西
-Need a hand with the boxes? -No, it's just this.
‎祝你今天愉快
Have a great day.
‎-加兰女士 ‎-鲍德温警探
-Ms. Garran. -Detective Baldwin.
‎谢谢你愿意见我
Oh, thank you for seeing me.
‎只要有助于把调查结束掉就行
Anything to help wrap this up.
‎是这样的 我有几个问题
So, I just have a couple of questions.
‎皮克斯报告里面 ‎有所有的药物取用记录
The "Pixie" report. You have all the drug withdrawals--
‎是皮克西
Uh, PYXIS.
‎没错
That's right.
‎这上面有所有护士的药物取用记录
Uh, so you've got all of the, um, drug withdrawals
‎-对吧？ ‎-没错
for all of the nurses on this?
‎我希望我能拿到完整的报告
That's correct.
Well, I was hoping I could get the full report,
‎因为这这上面只有 ‎安娜去世前很短一段时间内的
because this one only has a short window around Ana's expiration.
‎据我所知 ‎它只能存储最近四个星期的信息
I'm told it only stores the information for four weeks.
‎那你们在进行内部调查时 ‎应该拿到了一份记录 对吧？
Well, you must have gotten a copy during the internal investigation, right?
‎我记得没有 没有
I don't believe we did, no.
‎我倒是可以去查一下 ‎但是我们有的资料都寄给你们了
I mean, I can check, but, uh everything we had was sent to you.
‎你看 这是第九页
You see, this is page nine,
‎所以第一页到第八页 ‎应该还放在某个地方吧
so pages one to eight gotta be around here somewhere.
Hmm.
‎我一定会去查查看的
-Uh, I'll be sure to look into it.
‎加兰护士 ‎你的行为很像是在隐瞒证据啊
Nurse Garran, it's looking a lot like you're withholding some evidence here.
‎-我不太明白 ‎-就只有六页 其他的在哪里？
-I'm not sure I follow-- -Six pages. Where's the rest of it?
‎很抱歉 我还有一个会 推不掉
I'm sorry. I I have another meeting, and I can't shift it--
‎噢 我还没完呢
Oh, I'm not done.
‎我会和你办公室重新安排时间的
I'm gonna reschedule with your office.
‎坐下
Sit down.
‎-你说什么 ‎-给我他妈坐下！
-Excuse me-- -Sit the fuck down!
‎你很清楚自己在做什么
You know exactly what you're doing.
‎-大家好 ‎-嘿
-Hey, guys. -Hey.
‎我知道不该把婴儿带到这里
Um, I know you're not supposed to have babies in here,
‎但我实在找不到人照顾她
but I really didn't have anyone else who could take her.
‎-没关系 ‎-谢谢
-It's okay. -Thank you.
‎-她叫什么名字？ ‎-凡妮莎
-What's her name? -Vanessa.
‎邋遢妮莎
Messy Nessie.
‎-邋遢妮莎？ ‎-嗯
-Messy Nessie? -Uh-huh.
‎我有两个女儿 我明白的
Well, I have two girls, so I hear that.
‎她多大了？
-Mm. -How old is she?
‎六个月
Six months.
‎噢 她晚上能睡整觉了吗？
Oh. She sleeping through the night yet?
‎-不能 ‎-应该是长牙了
-No! -She must be teething.
‎-是啊 ‎-嗯
-Oh, yeah. -Uh-huh.
‎洛克伦护士？
Nurse Loughren? It's not urgent. There's a Code Purple in 300.
‎不是紧急情况 300房紫色代码了
‎好的
Oh, okay.
‎什么是“紫色代码”？
What's a Code Purple?
‎意思是披萨到了 你想来一块吗？
It means pizza's arrived. Do you want a slice?
‎哦
Oh.
‎我怎么拒绝得了披萨呢
Well, I can't say no to pizza.
‎当然拒绝不了了
You can't.
‎可惜的是 你吃不了披萨
Unfortunately, though, you're gonna have to say no to pizza.
‎好的
Okay.
‎但你恢复得很好 ‎很快就能抱凡妮莎了
But you are healing nicely, and will be holding Vanessa in no time.
‎她在电话里对我说了十五次让我去死
She told me to go fuck myself 15 times on the phone.
‎我的天啊
Oh my God.
‎这么不友善
That's not nice.
‎我还没跟你讲最精彩的部分呢
I haven't even told you the best part.
‎她为了不让我见女儿
So now, to try and stop me from seeing the girls,
‎还编了个故事 说我欺负她的狗
she has made up a story about me being mean to her dog.
‎我不是在开玩笑吗？越来越精彩了
I'm not kidding. It gets better and better.
‎老实说 如果这不是真事的话 ‎我也会觉得非常搞笑的
Honestly, the whole thing would be hilarious if it wasn't true.
‎我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
‎不 你在开玩笑吗？是我自己的错
No. Are you kidding? It's my own fault.
‎是我自己挑了个疯子
I picked a crazy.
Oh, you know, it works for me.
I mean, it's not, like quickly.
-Right. -What did you say?
Nothing. Nothing, bro.
-You said a word. I didn't.
‎再过两分钟 姑娘们
Two minutes, girls.
‎你要不要去拿书包和外套？
Okay. Do you wanna get your backpack and coat?
‎-你要扎马尾辫上学吗？ ‎-当然
-You want a ponytail for school? -Sure.
‎头发真漂亮
Beautiful hair.
‎真希望我们可以待在家里
I wish we could stay home.
‎我也希望
I wish that too.
‎-你要拿外套吗？爱你 ‎-好的 爱你
-Wanna get your jacket? -Yeah.
-Love you. -Love you.
‎里面还有什么？有什么新信息吗？
What else is in that? Anything new?
Um
‎是的 有一份安娜马丁内斯体内
Yeah, there was a list of all the medications
‎所有的药物记录
that were in Ana Martinez's system.
‎-胰岛素？ ‎-对 还有一样
-Insulin? -Yeah, and another one.
‎听好了 地高辛
Get this. Digoxin.
‎地高辛
-Digoxin?
‎鲍德温
Baldwin!
‎-你是认真的吗？ ‎-该死
-Are you serious? -Shit.
‎你吼她了？市议会的马尔科姆伯雷尔 ‎刚打电话过来了
Screaming at her.
Malcolm Burrel from City Council just called.
‎丹尼很愿意向加兰夫人道歉
Danny will be happy to apologize to Mrs. Garran.
‎太晚了 你俩都不准进入医院了
Well, too late. You've both been banned from the hospital property.
‎什么？
What?
‎总不能禁止我们去 ‎我们正在调查的犯罪现场啊
Can't ban us from the scene of a crime that we're investigating.
‎-什么犯罪？ ‎-凶杀案
-What crime? -Homicide.
‎你有什么根据啊？
What do you have to back this up?
‎这些档案 还有询问过一名护士
The files and an interview with a nurse
‎她确定受害者被注射了胰岛素
who was certain that the victim was given insulin.
‎什么受害者？
Victim, what victim?
‎安娜马丁内斯
Ana Martinez.
‎你没有尸体
You have no body.
‎没尸体就没法验尸 你知道规矩的
No body, no autopsy. You know how this works.
‎不准我们进他妈的医院？
Banned from the fuckin' hospital?
‎凯莉 汤姆打电话来问你了
Hey, Kelly. Tom called to check on you.
‎我根本忘不掉小凡妮莎有多可爱
I cannot get over how cute that little Vanessa is.
‎凡妮莎是谁？
Who's Vanessa?
‎凯莉 你知道你现在在哪里吗？
Kelly, do you know where you are right now?
‎我需要你回答我 亲
I need you to answer me, hon.
‎我在医院
I'm at the hospital.
‎哪家医院？
Which hospital?
Uh
‎好吧
All right.
‎捏我的手
Squeeze my hands.
‎来 捏我的手
Come on. Squeeze my hands.
‎力气有点小
A little light.
‎汤姆来了吗？
Has Tom come by?
‎他打电话过来问你了
He called to check on you.
‎-嘿 汤姆 我是医院的艾米 ‎-嗨 艾米 你好吗？
-Hey, Tom, it's Amy from the hospital. -Hi, Amy. What's going on?
‎我觉得你很有必要过来一下 ‎情况一夜之间发生了变化
I really think that you should come in. There's been a change overnight.
‎我觉得应该尽可能早点赶过来
I think you should come in sooner rather than later.
‎好 待会见
Okay, see you soon.
‎我去看过贝丝了 她还在睡觉
I checked in with Beth. She's still sleeping.
‎-杰克一直在按呼叫铃 ‎-我的天啊
-Jack's been pushing on his call button-- -Oh my God.
‎怎么了？
What?
‎她体内有胰岛素
There's insulin in her system.
‎紧急情况 西区
Code Blue. Wing West.
‎天啊！
Oh my God! Oh God!
‎不！
-No!
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
‎天啊！
Oh God!
‎我的天啊
Oh my God!
‎没事的
-It's okay.
‎可恶
Shit.
‎你好 很抱歉这样来打扰你
Hello. Sorry to bother you like this.
‎没事
Yeah, no.
‎我们需要你帮忙 艾米
We need your help, Amy.
‎抱歉 两位 我不知道她怎么了
Look, I'm sorry, guys. I Really, I don't know what happened to her.
‎谁怎么了？
To who?
‎凯莉安德森 我说的是
Kelly Anderson. I I mean
‎凯莉安德森是谁？
Who's Kelly Anderson?
‎又一个受害者吗？
Is there another victim?
‎又是双重用药差错吗？
Another double-medication error?
‎卡伦有跟凯莉安德森在一起过吗？
Was Cullen with Kelly Anderson?
‎这事和查理没关系
This has nothing to do with Charlie.
‎-你有多了解他？ ‎-非常了解
-How well do you know him? -Really well.
‎是吗？
Do you?
‎他在九家医院工作过
He's been at nine hospitals.
‎没有一家医院愿意回应我们
And none of 'em will talk to us.
‎你什么意思？我
What do you mean? I'm
‎如果有什么问题的话 ‎他就不可能再找到工作了
No. If something had happened, he wouldn't have been able to get a job.
‎-医院肯定会做些什么 ‎-事情理应如此
-The hospital would have done something. -You'd think so.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎他们在刻意回避我们
They're stonewalling us.
‎你必须帮帮我们
You have to help us.
‎妈妈 你进来吗？
Mom, are you coming?
‎嘿 宝贝 我马上就来 ‎你在里面等着 好吗？
Hey, honey. Yeah, I'll be in in a second. Just wait inside, okay?
‎好的
Okay.
‎两位 我现在没法聊 ‎我的孩子在这里 我
Guys, I can't talk right now. My kid's here. Like
‎好的 这是我的名片
Okay. Here's my card.
‎打电话给我 也许他和你想的不一样
Give me a call. Maybe he's not who you think.
‎祝你一天愉快
Have a nice day.
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎-你需要什么吗？ ‎-不用
-Do you need anything? -Mm-mm.
‎-不用吗？ ‎-我没事
-No? -I'm fine.
‎好的 如果觉得累就告诉我
Okay. You let me know if you feel tired.
‎不累 会告诉你的 我感觉很好
I'm not. I will. I feel good.
‎-是吗？ ‎-是的
-Yeah? -Yeah.
‎好的
-Okay. -Mm.
‎他妈的艾米洛克伦！
Amy fucking Loughren!
‎口袋火箭！
-Pocket Rocket! -Mm!
‎见到你真好
-It is so good to see you! -I know. You look so good.
‎是啊 你气色真好
‎-真的吗？ ‎-是啊 气色非常好
-Really? -Yes! You look great.
‎-谢谢 ‎-不客气
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
‎-我都筋疲力尽了 ‎-你好 可以点餐了吗？
-I feel exhausted. -Hi there! You ready to order?
‎-我要芝士煎蛋卷 ‎-好的
-Oh, I'll have a cheese omelet. -Okay.
‎-搭配什么最合适呢？ ‎-霞多丽葡萄酒
-And what pairs best with that? -Chardonnay.
‎一大杯冰镇霞多丽干白
Oh. A large cold glass of dry chardonnay.
‎-我也一样 谢谢 ‎-好 马上来
-Okay. -I'll have the same.
‎我们上次来这里是什么时候？
-Thanks. -Coming right up.
When was the last time we were in this dive?
‎很久以前 至少有十年了
A long time ago. Like, at least a decade.
‎-什么？ ‎-12年？
-What? -Twelve years?
‎天啊
-Ugh, Jesus.
‎-我老了 ‎-来了
-I'm getting old. -Here we go.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎保罗怎么样？
How's Paul?
‎我们分手了
Uh, we split up.
‎-妈呀 ‎-其实也没什么
-Oh shit. -I mean, it's not a big deal.
‎那是很久之前的事了 ‎我们现在一起养狗
It was a long time ago, and we share custody of the dogs.
‎好不容易才达成了协议 ‎我很开心你打电话来了
We worked hard to come to that agreement. I'm so glad that you called.
‎我也是
Mm! Me too.
‎只不过 我想问你点事 有些奇怪
Just, you know, I wanted to I wanted to ask you
It's It's a little weird.
‎我喜欢奇怪的事
I love weird.
‎你记不记得和一个 ‎叫查理卡伦的人工作过？
But, um do you remember working with someone named Charlie Cullen?
‎-记得 ‎-是吗？
-Yeah. -Yeah?
‎为什么问这个？
Why?
‎我现在在帕克菲尔德和他一起工作
Well, I'm working with him right now at Parkfield.
‎有一个关于他的传闻
There was a rumor about him.
‎有一起死亡是他的责任
That he was responsible for a death.
‎他导致了某人用药过量
That he OD'd someone.
‎哦
Oh.
‎用了什么药物
Uh, with what?
‎他们在死者的生理盐水袋里 ‎发现了胰岛素
They found insulin in the dead guy's saline bag.
‎有好几袋
They found it in a few.
‎储藏室中盐水袋上有针孔
Pinpricks in the ones in the store.
‎有人在盐水袋还没拿出去前 ‎就往里面加了东西
Somebody had dosed them before they went out.
‎他们为什么会怀疑是查理干的？
Why did they think it was Charlie?
‎他们没怀疑
They didn't.
‎以前我们每晚总会遇到紧急情况 ‎有时候两到三次
But we used to get codes every night. Sometimes two or three.
‎但自从他离开后
And then after he left,
‎我们一个月就只有一次了
we got, like, only one a month.
‎你们也有很多紧急情况吗？
You get a lot of codes?
Okay.
‎天啊
Oh God.
‎噢！
Oh!
‎嘿
Hmm.
Hey.
‎放松
Easy, easy.
‎没事了 没事的
You're okay. You're okay. It's okay.
‎艾米 没事了
-Amy, it's okay.
‎你在急救科里 你现在情况很稳定
You're in the ED. You're doing great.
‎我去看过女儿们了 ‎洁姬和她们在一起
I checked on the girls. Jackie's with them.
‎我可以带她们过来
I can go get 'em, bring 'em here.
‎-不要 ‎-不要吗？好的
- No. -No? Okay.
‎要喝水吗？
You want some water?
‎不用吗？
No?
‎请别再像这样吓我了
Don't you ever scare me like that again please.
‎我想走
-I wanna leave. -I know, I know.
‎我知道
‎我明白
I get it.
‎我们不会让他们知道的
We're not gonna let them find out.
‎护士在哪里？
Where Where's the nurse?
‎别担心 最近一次血压测量结果很好
Uh, don't worry. Your last pressure looked pretty good.
‎你的心率最近一小时都在80以下
Your heart rate's been below 80 for the last hour.
‎我看了检查结果 肌钙蛋白偏高 ‎但是有下降的趋势
I saw the labs, and your troponin's high, but it's trending down.
‎所以你的情况很好 不会有事的
So you're good. You're okay.
‎已经运气很好了 有可能会非常糟
You're lucky. Could've been a lot worse.
‎-我想回家 ‎-我知道
-I wanna go home. -I know.
‎-好 ‎-喂 看到她的心率上升了
-Okay. -Hey. Saw her heart rate blip up.
‎你醒了？
-You awake? -Yeah--
‎-是的 ‎-把出院表给我拿来
Bring me a discharge form.
‎嘿 我觉得这不是个好主意 ‎她应该再多住一晚
Hey. I don't think that's a good idea. She should stay overnight.
‎-嗯 我们没问题的 ‎-我想违背医嘱出院
-Yeah, we got this. -I wanna leave AMA.
‎你确定吗？
-You sure?
‎我会开车送她回去 ‎确保她有人照顾 谢谢
I'll drive her home. Make sure she's looked after. Thank you.
‎我们没事了 谢谢
-We're good. Thank you.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎请别这样了
-Please, stop.
‎好的
Okay.
‎胳膊给我
Give me your arm.
‎你确定不要我进去吗？
So you sure you don't want me to come in?
‎我很高兴睡在沙发上 我可以
I'm happy to sleep on the couch. I can
‎-我可以送女儿们去学校 ‎-我不想吓到她们
-I can take the girls to school. -I don't wanna scare them.
‎不会有事的 我只是需要睡觉
Nothing's gonna happen. I just I just need to sleep.
‎你说得对
-You're right.
‎-谢谢你 查理 ‎-好的
-Thanks, Charlie. -Yeah.
‎但如果你需要什么的话
But if you need anything
‎我会给你打电话的
I'll call you.
‎是吧？
Yeah?
‎只剩一个月了 艾米
It's a month, Amy.
‎我们能挺过去的
We got this.
‎你身上好冰 快去吧
You're freezing. Go.
‎好的
‎给我打电话哦
Call me.
‎必须要保密
It has to be a secret.
‎天啊
Oh God.
‎不能让任何人知道
No one can know.
‎我会被开除的
I'll get fired.
‎明白
Understood.
‎他是在储藏室里干的
He does it in the storage room
‎盐水袋还没拿出去前
before it even goes out.
‎他就往里面注射了胰岛素
He injects the insulin into the bags,
‎因为这样胰岛素会缓慢地进入血液
and because it enters the bloodstream slowly,
‎所以需要几个小时甚至一天才会致死
it could take hours or even, you know, a day to kill someone.
‎他不用接触就能把人给杀了
So he's killing 'em without ever touching 'em.
‎除了胰岛素之外 ‎他可能在盐水袋里放别的东西吗？
Could he put something other than insulin inside those bags?
‎是的 任何透明液体都不会被察觉
Yeah, any clear liquid wouldn't be detected.
‎地高辛是透明液体吗？
Is digoxin a clear liquid?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎会致人死吗？
Could it kill someone?
‎你见了的那个护士 ‎她会愿意见我们吗？
Okay, and the nurse you met with, you think she'll talk to us?
‎不
No.
‎不 会让她丢掉工作的
No, she'll lose her job.
‎你介意看下我们 ‎从帕克菲尔德拿到的资料吗？
Do you mind taking a look at what we got here from Parkfield?
‎剩下的呢？
Where's the rest of it?
‎就这些 我们只有这些 ‎他们给我们的都在这里了
That's it. That's all we have. That's all they gave us.
‎皮克西的报告就只有两页
The PYXIS report's just two pages.
‎他们说药品柜只能保存四星期的记录
They said it only keeps the file for four weeks.
‎不对 那是电脑啊
No, it's a computer.
‎安装之后的信息都会一直保存 是
It keeps the information for as long as it was installed. It's
‎我会把查理的皮克西报告 ‎从我病房的机器里调出来
I'll pull Charlie's PYXIS report from the machine in my ward,
‎我们就用那个来证明安娜去世的时候
and we'll use that to prove that he withdrew insulin
‎他取用了胰岛素和地高辛
and digoxin when Ana died.
‎好的 问题是安娜马丁内斯被火化了
Yeah, see, the problem is that Ana Martinez was cremated,
‎我们没有验尸报告
so we don't have an autopsy.
‎我们需要实实在在的遗体
What we need is an actual body.
‎（查询：卡伦）
‎（打印报告）
‎（病人：杰克艾文斯 ‎用药：地高辛溶胶）
‎（病人：休鲁珀森 ‎用药：地高辛溶胶‎）
‎（病人：丽贝卡布拉格 ‎用药：胰岛素10毫升）
‎如你所知 我们得到了 ‎凯莉安德森丈夫的许可
As you know, we got permission from Kelly Anderson's husband
‎去把她的遗体挖出来检验
to dig up her body for examination.
‎根据尸检结果我们发现她的体内 ‎有胰岛素和地高辛的混合物
From the autopsy, we know that a combination of insulin and digoxin
‎导致她在15号凌晨去世
were in Kelly's system and led to her death
in the early hours of the 15th.
‎对了 然后是14号 22点47分的时候
Right, and then on the 14th at 20:47,
‎你可以看到查理从皮克西药品柜中 ‎取用了胰岛素和地高辛
you see that Charlie took out insulin and digoxin from the PYXIS.
‎如果你再看凯莉的报告
And if you see Kelly's report,
‎她是血糖在21点56分降低
her blood sugar just drops at 21:56,
‎所以这就是胰岛素起作用了
so that is the insulin taking effect.
‎22点15分心率减缓
And there's slow arrhythmia at 22:15,
‎那是地高辛
and that's digoxin.
‎所以他掌握着两种凶器 ‎死亡时间是3点57分
So he was holding two murder weapons. 3:57 is the time of death.
‎一切都清楚了
Everything's there.
‎等下 稍等
Wait a second. Hold on.
‎这个皮克西报告上说取消了 ‎没有取出
With this PYXIS, it says cancellations, not withdrawals.
‎是这个系统的故障
Well, it's a fault in the system.
‎如果最后按取消的话 ‎抽屉还是会打开的
So when you cancel at the last minute, the drawer opens,
‎但报告会显示取消
but it reports it as a cancellation.
‎卡伦知道这件事吗？
And Cullen knows about that?
‎是的 我看他这么做过
Yeah, and I saw him do it.
‎胰岛素 地高辛 这里有几百条记录
Insulin, digoxin. There's hundreds of orders here.
‎好吧 但这上面不是这样写的 ‎从这上面看 他从来没取用过
Okay, but not according to this. This makes it look like he never got 'em.
‎但他就是取了
But he did.
‎你亲眼见他这么做过吗？
Did you actually see him do this?
‎各位 这是证据确凿啊
Guys, this is the smoking gun right here.
‎不 这不是
Yeah, but this isn't.
‎只是取消记录 看不出有什么预谋
It's just cancellations. There's nothing nefarious.
‎无法证明有罪 这
There's no proof of guilt. There's--
‎他一到帕克菲尔德 就开始这样做了
Okay, he's been doing this since he started at Parkfield, so look.
‎你看 全是反复取消的记录 对吧？
Look at all of these repeated cancellations, right?
‎看 在取消之后 ‎也从没接上正确的药单
Look. They're not followed up with a correct order.
‎他只是在反复取用维库溴铵和地高辛
He's had repeated orders of vec and digoxin.
‎说真的 这很明显有问题 这
I mean, it's really-- It just screams wrong. It's
‎也许吧 ‎也许只是帕克菲尔德院方不懂呢
Maybe. Maybe Parkfield just didn't understand.
‎不可能的 各位 ‎琳达加兰以前也是护士
Come on, guys. Linda Garran used to be a nurse.
‎她懂
She understood.
‎肯定的 她知道 可她什么都没做
Oh yeah, she knows, and she's not doing anything.
‎卡伦护士 感谢你在休息时赶过来
Nurse Cullen, thank you for coming in on your day off.
‎嗨 你叫我查理就行
Hi, you can call me Charlie.
‎我们发现了一些令人担忧的事
Uh We've come across something troubling.
‎你在这里工作之前在哪个医院任职？
What hospital were you employed at before you took the position here?
‎圣伊丽莎白
St. Elizabeth's.
‎你在那里工作的具体日期是？
And what were your dates of employment there?
Uh
‎我不太确定 ‎是圣伊丽莎白出了什么问题吗？
I'm not sure. Is there an issue from St. Elizabeth's?
‎因为我当时被一些同事盯上了 ‎我不知道 是不是他们又来
'Cause I was targeted by some coworkers. I don't know. Maybe they're at it again.
‎我们关心的是你在申请表上填的日期
What we're concerned with are the dates you listed on your application.
‎你还记得是什么吗？
Do you remember what they were?
Um
‎六月一号到八月三号 好像是
June '01 to August '03, maybe.
‎-是的 你是那样写的 ‎-对
-Yes, that's what you wrote. -Right.
‎这些日期不对 卡伦先生
Those dates are incorrect, Mr. Cullen.
‎哦
Oh.
‎圣伊丽莎白跟我们确认了 ‎你是五月入职的
St. Elizabeth's confirmed with us that you were employed from May,
‎所以你申请表上的出入
so these discrepancies on your application form
‎让我们别无选择 只能让你
leave us with no option but to let you go
‎即刻离职
with immediate effect.
‎等等 就因为申请表上填错了个日期 ‎你们就要把我开除？
Wait, so you're firing me for writing the wrong dates on my application?
‎合约里有这条
It It is in the contract.
‎我是不是还要签个字什么的？
Well, I believe I need to sign something.
‎就这些吗？
Is that all?
‎就这些
That's all.
‎谢谢你 卡伦先生
Thank you, Mr. Cullen.
‎我刚收到帕克菲尔德的消息 ‎他们把卡伦的问题处理好了
I just got news from Parkfield. They've dealt with the Cullen issue.
‎-这话什么意思？ ‎-他被开除了
-What does that mean? -He's been fired.
‎-什么？ ‎-他们就这样放他走了？
-What? -So they're just gonna let him go?
‎他们是怎么说的？
Well, what did they say?
‎他们把他开除了 ‎因为在他的文档里发现了一些出入
That they fired him because they found some discrepancy in his paperwork.
‎那他当时的状态如何？稳定吗？
Well, what was his state of mind? Was he stable?
‎等等 你们不会觉得 ‎这样会让他变得更危险吧？
Wait, you don't think that this could make him more dangerous, do you?
‎至少他不能再接近病人了
At least he can't be anywhere near patients.
‎他没办法伤人了
He can't hurt anyone.
‎他在九家医院都待过 九家
He's been at nine hospitals. Nine.
‎你还不明白吗？
What don't you understand?
‎他们都说了同样的话 ‎掩盖自己的责任
They all say the same thing. They cover up their own liabilities.
‎这种事一次又一次地出现
It happens again and again and again.
‎他会在另一家医院找到新工作 ‎一切会照旧
He's gonna get a new job at another hospital,
and it's all gonna continue.
‎是你纵容的
You allowed this.
‎别看我 确实如此
Don't look at me.
You did.
‎-洁姬 我回来了 ‎-玛雅
-Jackie, I'm back. -Maya.
‎-我的天！ ‎-玛雅！你不能好好说你的台词吗？
-Oh my God! -Maya! Can you just say your line?
‎嘿 姑娘们
Hey, girls.
‎我忘了
I forgot it.
‎哇喔
Wow.
‎什么？
What?
‎你不是有剧本吗？
Don't you have the script?
‎-我没有剧本 ‎-我的天啊
-I don't have the script. -Oh my God.
‎好吧 我弄丢了
Okay, I lost it.
‎玛雅 你这都是第几次了
Maya, you've done this so many times!
‎亚历克斯 对你妹妹好点
Okay, Alex, be nice to your sister.
‎-玛雅演的是查理的角色 ‎-嘿
Maya's speaking over Charlie's part again.
‎你来这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
‎排练
Rehearsing.
‎洁姬呢？
Where's Jackie?
‎我跟她说她可以回家了 ‎今晚就只有我们了
I told her she could go home. It was just gonna be us tonight.
‎我们做好饭了
We cooked!
‎-是的 ‎-是查理做的
-We did. -Charlie cooked.
‎-我帮忙了 ‎-不 你没有
-I helped. -No, you didn't.
‎-不 我有！ ‎-不 你没有
-Yes, I did! -No, you didn't.
‎-不 我有！ ‎-亚历克斯 是我们一起煮的
-Yes, I did! -Alex, we all cooked.
‎妈妈 你为什么怪怪的？
Why are you being weird, Mom?
‎我没有
I'm not.
‎-我们做了一餐很特别的饭 ‎-是他妈妈的秘方
-We're making something special. -It's his mom's recipe.
‎-来 ‎-很好吃
-Come. -Yummy!
‎坐下 放松一下 ‎观赏《哈姆德拉姆佛斯的镇长》
Sit, relax. Enjoy the "Mayor of Humdrum Falls."
‎要不要让你们妈妈 ‎来扮演莫普霍普斯利？
Should we get your mom to play Mop Hopsley?
‎-好啊 ‎-好吗？
-Yeah. -Yeah?
‎亚历克斯
Alex
‎玛雅 请过来
Maya, please come here.
‎-为什么？ ‎-因为我让你们过来 过来
-Why? -'Cause I'm asking you to. Come here.
‎我不想来
I don't want to.
‎嘿 去你妈妈那里
Hey, go to your mom.
‎过来
Get over here.
‎立刻过来！
Get over here right now!
‎可为什么啊？我玩得正开心呢
But why? I'm having fun.
‎回到你们房间去 去吧
Go to your room. Go.
‎她怎么这么生气？
Why is she so angry?
‎我不知道
I don't know.
‎看来你已经听说了
So I'm guessing you heard.
‎是的
Yeah.
‎她说为什么了吗？
She say why?
Mm-mm.
‎他们把我开除了 ‎就因为我申请表上的日期写错了
They fired me because I wrote the wrong dates on my application form apparently.
‎哦
Oh.
‎-是的 ‎-是啊
-Yeah. -Yeah.
‎今天真是疯狂啊
It's been a wacko day.
‎最近几个月都很疯狂 其实是
It's been a wacko couple of months. Actually it's Ugh.
‎我本来不是来这里工作的
You know, I wasn't even meant to be working here.
‎我接受这份工作是因为 ‎我想离我的孩子近点
I took this job because I wanted to be close to my kids.
‎可我来到这里后 ‎她连见都不让我见她们
Then when I get here, she won't even let me see them,
‎然后她开始编瞎话 说我给狗下毒
and then she starts making up this insane stuff about poisoning the dog,
‎现在又这样 真是
and then this, you know
‎我觉得是老天爷恨我 艾米
I think the universe hates me, Amy.
‎-真的 ‎-查理
-Really. -Charlie--
‎-我不得不信 ‎-不是这样的
-At this point. -You know that's not true.
‎我真的很抱歉 这种事发生在你身上
I'm really sorry this happened to you.
‎不用这样 我才抱歉呢 ‎因为我知道你还有三周时间
No, please. I'm sorry, 'cause I know you've still got three more weeks,
‎可我却没办法在院里帮你了
and I'm not gonna be there to help.
‎但我可以在这里帮你
But I can I can help here.
‎我可以照顾她们 可以保证你有饭吃
I can, like, look after them, I can make sure you eat.
‎无论你需要什么
Anything you need.
‎真的 什么都可以
Really. Anything.
‎我都乐意
That's all right.
‎我有没有告诉你 ‎前两天亚历克斯发火了？
Did I tell you Alex blew up the other day?
‎-没有 ‎-是的
-No. -Yeah.
‎她大发雷霆
She just lost it.
‎她当时又哭又喊 十分挣扎
She was crying and screaming, and, like
She's really struggling.
‎我工作太忙了 所以
I'm working so much, so
‎很抱歉 我知道 确实不容易
I'm so sorry. I mean, you know, it's a lot, you know?
‎对我来说真正需要的是
But what I think would be really helpful to me is, um
‎让我和她们多待在一起
if I could spend some time alone with them, you know?
‎只有我和女儿们
Just me and the girls.
‎我知道现在跟你说这种话真的不合适
And I feel really bad saying this to you,
‎因为我知道你今天也非常难受
because I know that this has been a day from hell for you.
‎老实说 查理 你这一年简直糟透了
I mean, Charlie, honestly, you've had the year from hell.
‎没事
No.
‎还有
And, um
‎我真希望我能在你身边
God, I wish I could be there for you.
‎可我感觉糟透了 实在太对不起了
-I just feel like shit. I'm so sorry. -No.
‎不 艾米 别说了 我懂 别说了
Amy, stop. I get it. Please.
‎她们是你的孩子 她们需要你
It's It's your kids. They need this.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎你是个好妈妈
And you're a good mom.
‎说真的 看着我
-No, look at me.
‎你是个好妈妈
You're a good mom.
Mm.
‎-好吧 ‎-很高兴我能帮上忙
-Okay. -I'm glad I can help.
‎答应我你一定要吃饭
Promise me you'll eat.
‎闻起来很香
-It smells good.
‎毕竟是我妈的秘方嘛
It's my mom's recipe, you know.
‎-好的 ‎-你知道吗？光是能这样
-Okay. -You know what?
Just, actually, just, like, sitting here, talking to you,
‎坐在这里 跟你聊天
‎跟你们在一起
being with you
‎让我意识到一切都会好起来的
it made me realize everything's gonna be okay.
‎我还有你
I've got you.
‎我有玛雅和亚历克斯 ‎还有我的女儿们
I got Maya and Alex. I got my girls.
‎不过就是份工作 我还能再找的
It's a job. I can get a job.
‎没问题的
You can.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎晚安
Night.
‎查理 嘿
Charlie? Hey.
‎噢 嘿
Oh, hey.
‎-我刚才 ‎-没事吧？
-I was, um-- -You okay?
‎没事！我
Yes! I
‎我想向你道歉 ‎我昨天的行为这么奇怪
You know, I wanna apologize for being so weird yesterday.
‎昨晚 我只是
Like, last night, it was just
‎-没事 别说了 ‎-对不起
-No. Stop. Sorry.
‎我走后 ‎你有没有好好陪陪亚历克斯？
Did you and Alex get some time after I left?
‎有 谢谢你
We did. Yeah, thank you.
‎是吗？很好啊
Yeah? Oh, good.
‎我觉得觉得你俩确实都很需要
I think You know, I think that you Like, both of you needed that.
Mm!
‎很高兴能帮上忙
I'm glad I could help.
‎我要去上班了
You You know, I'm about to go to work, and
‎查理 你不在那儿了我觉得很不习惯
Charlie, it bothers me so much that you're not gonna be there.
‎我知道 我也想你
I know. I know. I miss you too.
‎你想去公园玩玩吗？和女儿们一起？
You wanna go to the park or something? With the girls?
‎（午餐）
Um
‎艾米？
Amy?
‎要不午餐吧
Uh, maybe lunch?
‎-好啊 ‎-好的
-Uh, yeah. Okay.
‎午餐可以啊 什么时间呢？
Lunch. Uh Lunch works. When's good?
‎让我想想
Uh, let me think
for a moment.
Um
‎周六？
Saturday?
‎好啊 周六可以
Uh Yeah. Saturday works.
‎我现在要去上班了 所以
But I have to go to work now, so I'll find a place.
‎-我选个地方 再把具体信息发给你 ‎-给我发短信就好
-Just text me -I'll I'll I'll send you the details.
‎-好的 ‎-好的 再见
-Okay. -Okay, bye.
‎-替我向桑德拉问好 ‎-我会的
-Say hi to Sandra for me. -Oh, I will.
‎-好的 再见 ‎-再见
-Okay. Bye. -Bye.
‎回头见 再见
See you later. Bye-bye.
‎非常好 你还记得我们聊过什么吗？
Great job.
So you remember what we talked about?
‎我们能阻止他的唯一办法是让他承认
The only way we can stop him is if he admits to doing it,
‎所以必须让他认罪
so we gotta get him to confess.
‎操
Oh fuck. Um
‎唉 她的脉搏在加速
Man, her pulse is racing.
‎希望你们能听到我说话
Okay, well, I hope you guys can hear me.
‎好了
Right.
‎我操
Oh fuck.
‎操
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
‎他走进来了
He's walking in right now.
‎嘿！
Hey!
‎嘿
Hey.
‎你好
Hello.
‎嗨 最近如何啊？
Hi. How's it going?
‎唉 你知道的
Well, you know.
‎-你还好吗？ ‎-嗯
-You okay? -Yeah.
‎是吗
-Yeah? -Yeah.
‎我喜欢这里
I like this place.
‎最近怎么样？
What's going on?
Whew.
‎你们要喝些什么吗？
So can I get you guys something to drink?
‎-我要一杯冰红茶 谢谢 ‎-冰红茶
-Uh, I'll get an iced tea, please. -Iced tea.
‎我要水就行 谢谢
I will just have water. Thanks.
‎你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
‎我今晚要开始新工作了 ‎希望能给大家留下好印象
I'm starting a new job tonight. Hoping these will make a good impression.
‎-在哪里啊？ ‎-埃尔姆斯沃斯
-Where? -Elmsworth.
‎-你要去埃尔姆斯沃斯上班啊？ ‎-是啊 今晚开始
-You're starting at Elmsworth tonight? -Yeah. Tonight, yeah.
‎我的东西都装在车上了 ‎准备好重新开始了
Got all my stuff in the car, ready for a new start.
‎那真是哇 查理
That's Wow, Charlie.
‎可以点餐了吗？
You ready to order?
‎我要一个芝士汉堡
Oh. Uh You know, I'll get a I'll get a cheeseburger.
‎我也是
-Me too. -All right.
‎好的 两个芝士汉堡
-So -Two cheeseburgers, please!
‎女儿们还好吗？
How are the girls?
‎-谢谢 ‎-她们都挺好的
-Thank you. -They're really good.
‎镇长怎么样？
How's the mayor?
‎她很好
Yeah, she's great.
‎感觉好点了吗？
Feeling better?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎你不在那里 工作就很辛苦了
Work's been pretty awful without you there.
‎我们就像搭档
We were like partners.
‎我知道
I know.
‎最糟糕的地方 ‎就是大家一直在说你的坏话
And, like, the worst part is
that everyone is just, you know,
talking shit about you all the time.
‎我猜到了 是啊
I guessed they would. Yeah.
‎我觉得很生气 ‎因为你不能为自己辩护
It makes me mad 'cause you're not there to defend yourself, and so
‎所以我和所有人发生了争执 桑德拉
You know, I'm going to town on everyone, and Sandra, she--
‎天哪
Oh God!
‎她被我骂了一顿
-Oh, she got an earful.
‎现在他们也开始说我的坏话了
Now they'll be talking shit about me.
‎我不想谈帕克菲尔德 这个
I don't wanna talk about Parkfield. It's
‎为什么不呢？
Why not?
‎是因为
Is it because
‎他们说的都是真的吗？
what they're saying's true?
‎你知道吗
'Cause, you know, um
‎假如那些事真是你干的 ‎我也不会在乎的
I wouldn't care if you did those things.
‎我的意思是 我能理解
I mean, I could understand.
‎你可以解释
-You could explain it--
‎我还没告诉你 她允许我见女儿们了
I didn't tell you. I got permission to see my girls.
‎每隔一周可以见两天
Two days every second week.
‎我在想也许你、玛雅和亚历克斯 ‎还有我和我的女儿们
I was thinking I don't know, I was thinking
that maybe you and Maya and Alex and then me and my girls,
‎可以一起去一日游什么的
we could go on a day trip or something.
‎我想探谈谈帕克菲尔德
I wanna talk about Parkfield.
‎我想谈谈你做了什么
I wanna talk about what you did.
♪ That love will sometimes bring
‎我得走了
I gotta go.
‎我刚找到新工作 不能迟到 所以
I'm starting a new job. Can't be late, so
‎但我很快会打给你的
But I'll call soon.
‎他要走了 各位 他要走了 ‎他现在正走出来
He's leaving. You guys, he's leaving. He's walking out right now.
What
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎埃尔姆斯沃斯在哪里？ ‎艾米 埃尔姆斯沃斯医院在哪里？
Where's Elmsworth? Amy, where's Elmsworth Hospital?
‎距离宾州50公里
Thirty miles away in Pennsylvania.
‎我去给埃利斯打电话
I'm gonna call Ellis.
‎我把他逼得太紧了
I pushed him too hard.
‎你做得很好 艾米
You did great, Amy.
‎一切都在掌握之中 ‎我们会把他抓起来的
We're good. They're gonna pick him up.
‎-好的 ‎-带他抓起来
-All right. -Bring him in.
‎我们只能拘留他48小时
We can only hold him for 48 hours.
‎跟他们聊一聊
-And talk to the people.
‎我要确保我心里的东西
And I'm gonna make sure there's something in my mind that
‎举起来手来
Show me your hands.
‎开门
Open the door.
‎慢慢地打开门
Slowly. Open the door.
‎你被捕了 下车 慢慢来
You're under arrest. Get out of the vehicle. Slowly.
‎趴在地上
Get down on the ground.
‎把这只手放在背后
Put this hand behind your back.
‎把另一只手放在背后 待在这里 别动
Put this other hand behind your back. Stay right there. Do not move.
‎我是蒂姆布劳恩警探 ‎和我一起的是丹鲍德温警探
My name is Detective Sergeant Tim Braun. With me is Detective Dan Baldwin.
‎今天是2003年12月13日 周六
Today is Saturday, December 13, 2003.
‎现在时间大约是晚上8点14分
The time is approximately 8:14 p.m.
‎我们现在是在重案组 ‎审讯室询问查尔斯卡伦
We're in the Major Crimes interview room with Mr. Charles Cullen.
‎卡伦先生 为了记录需要 ‎请你说出你的全名
Mr. Cullen, for the record, could you please state your full name?
‎查尔斯卡伦
Uh, Charles Cullen.
‎你能拼写一下吗？
Could you spell that, please?
‎C-H-A-R-L-E-S C-U-L-L-E-N
Uh, C-H-A-R-L-E-S
C-U-L-L-E-N.
‎那我们可以叫你查理吗？
Is it okay if we call you Charlie, then?
‎可以
Yeah.
‎好的
Okay.
‎好的 查理
Okay, Charlie.
‎你有什么想告诉我们的吗 查理？
Is there anything you wanna tell us, Charlie?
Um
‎应该没有吧 没有
I mean, uh I don't think so, no.
‎你在帕克菲尔德纪念医院 ‎污染了多少输液袋？
How many IV bags have you polluted at Parkfield Memorial Hospital?
‎我们知道是你杀了凯莉安德森
We know you killed Kelly Anderson.
‎我们知道你杀了安娜马丁内斯 ‎我们知道还有其他人
We know you killed Ana Martinez. We know there's others.
‎我们只想和你谈谈 查理
We just wanna talk about it with you, Charlie.
‎没有医院律师在场的话 ‎我不能谈论病人的事
I can't. I'm not meant to talk about patients
without the hospital lawyers.
‎你已经不在那里工作了 ‎你想说什么都可以
You don't work there anymore. You can say whatever you want.
‎是的 你可以在这里畅所欲言
You're free to talk here.
‎我不能 所以
I can't, so
‎你为什么要杀她们？
Why'd you kill 'em?
‎只有女人吗 查理？
Was it just women, Charlie?
‎也许她们让你想起了你的前妻？
They remind you of your ex-wife maybe?
‎那样的话我很能理解
You know, that I could understand.
‎还是你妈妈？
Or your mother?
‎我不能
I can't.
‎用生理盐水袋这招
You know, the the saline-bag stuff,
‎真的很聪明
that was was pretty smart.
‎这样做非常聪明 查理
That was very smart, Charlie.
‎我从没见过这样的方式
You know, I never seen anything like that.
‎你是怎么想到的？
How'd you come up with that?
‎你杀了多少人 查理？
How many have you killed, Charlie?
‎10个 还是11个？
Ten, 11?
‎查理 跟我聊聊 可以吗？
Hey, Charlie, stick with me here, okay?
‎抬起头来 查理
Come on back, Charlie.
‎我们只是想跟你谈谈 ‎我知道你可以的
Just gotta have this conversation, okay? I know you can do it.
‎我不能
I can't
‎查理 你能看着我吗？
Charlie, can you look at me, please?
‎-我不能 ‎-别这样 查理
Mm I can't.
-Come on, Charlie. -I can't.
‎你可以的  你必须这样做 ‎我知道你可以的
You can. You gotta do this. I know you can.
‎嘿
-Hey--
‎我不能
I can't. I can't.
‎查理
-Charlie.
‎-我不能 ‎-查理 你可以的
-Charlie. -I can't.
-I can't. -Charlie, you can.
‎我不能
I can't, I can't, I can't.
‎查理！
I can't, I can't.
Charlie!
‎好吧
All right.
‎我们看了你的护理记录
We've seen your Cerner, we've seen your PYXIS,
‎看了你的皮克西报告 ‎看了你的取药信息
we've seen your orders, we've seen the cancellations.
‎看到了你的取消记录 ‎我们全都知道了
We know all about it.
‎我们知道你是怎么 ‎给储藏室里的盐水袋下毒的
We know how you poisoned the bags in the storeroom,
‎让别的护士来输液
had the other nurses hang 'em up.
‎你猜怎么着？ ‎我猜凯莉不是你选的 对吧？
You know what? I don't think you picked Kelly, did you?
‎对吧？
Did you?
‎你知道我一直在好奇什么吗？
You know what I've been wondering?
‎我是不会评断你的 查理 听着
Now, I got no judgment. Charlie. Listen.
‎-我不能 ‎-嘿
-I can't. -Hey.
‎-你可以的 查理 你可以的 ‎-我不能
I can't.
-You can, Charlie. Yes, you can. -I can't.
‎我不能
I can't.
-Hey. -I can't.
‎-嘿 ‎-我不能
I can't.
‎喂 别给我搞这个了 ‎你他妈够了 查理！
-Hey. -I can't.
Hey, enough of this shit! Enough of this shit, Charlie!
‎我不能！
I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't!
‎我不能！
I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't!
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿
-Hey. -Hi.
‎怎么样了？
What happened?
‎我们是拿不到了
We're not gonna get it.
‎怎么也撬不开他 他不会认罪的
He's not gonna break. He's not gonna confess.
‎明天早上我们必须得把他放了
We have to release him tomorrow morning.
‎对不起
I'm sorry.
What's something a pet hamster spends a lot of time doing?
A pet hamster spends a lot of time in the cage.
-In the cage? -Yes!
In the cage!
Oh no!
‎你确定要这么做吗？
You sure you're up for this?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎记住 你不能碰他
Remember, you can't touch him.
‎甚至不能靠近他
You can't even get close to him.
‎他是我的朋友
He was my friend.
‎我只是想见见他
I just need to see him.
‎嗨 查理
Hi, Charlie.
‎你能把他的手铐摘掉吗？
Can you take his handcuffs off please?
‎求你了
Please?
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
Um
‎走吧 艾米
Go away, Amy.
‎你冷吗？
You cold?
‎你都冻僵了 来 我把这个披在你肩上
Look, you're freezing. Here.
I'm just gonna put this over your shoulders.
‎好了
There you go.
‎这几个月以来 ‎我真的很需要你 你知道吗？
I really needed you these few months, you know?
‎却碰上了这种事
And then all this.
‎这让我
It made me
‎忘了你对我有多重要
forget who you were to me.
‎忘了你为我做的事
Forget what you did for me, and
‎我忘了你的善良
I forgot about your goodness.
‎我永远不会明白
I'll never understand.
‎你这么善良慷慨的人
Not how you,
who is so kind and generous
‎怎么会去伤害人
how you could hurt people.
‎我很抱歉
And I'm so sorry
‎我对你说了谎 还背叛了你
that I lied to you and went behind your back.
‎这一定让你觉得更加孤单了
That must make you feel even more alone.
‎嘿
Hey. Hey.
‎我从来没有 ‎我只是想要帮助你
All You know, I never had
You know, I always just wanted to help you.
‎我知道
I know.
‎这点我知道
I know that.
‎我依旧需要你
And I still need you.
‎你需要我做什么？
What do you need me to do?
‎把真相说出来
Tell the truth.
‎是我做的
I just did it.
‎我也不知道为什么
‎对不起 这样还不够
I'm sorry. I'm gonna need more than that.
‎你想让我告诉你什么？
What do you want me to tell you?
‎名字
Names.
‎我记不起全部的名字来
I can't remember all the names.
‎把你记得的告诉我就行
Just tell me what you can remember.
‎道格拉斯史蒂文森
Douglas Stevenson.
‎安娜马丁内斯
Ana Martinez.
‎凯莉安德森
Kelly Anderson.
‎还有
And there there was
‎我不记得他的名字了 他很年轻
Uh
I can't remember his name. He was younger. Um
‎-杰克艾文斯？ ‎-对 杰克
-Jack Ivins? -Yeah. Jack.
‎杰克 对
Jack. Yep.
‎然后上一家医院还有个男的
And then there there was a
There was a a man at my last hospital,
‎他有个德国名字 我记不
uh, he had a German name. I can't
‎为什么？
Why?
‎他们没有阻止我
They didn't stop me.
‎（为了避免死刑）
‎（查尔斯卡伦承认谋杀了29人）
‎（实际的受害者数量 ‎被认为可能有400人之多）
‎（他从未解释过他的动机）
‎（查理卡伦目前正在 ‎新泽西州立监狱）
‎（服连续18次的无期徒刑）
‎（在2403年前都不得申请假释）
‎（卡伦当了16年护士）
‎（他工作过的大多数医院 ‎都对他有过怀疑）
‎（但没有一家阻止过他）
‎（也从未有任何人对这些医院）
‎（提起过刑事诉讼）
Mm.
‎我们该起床了 今天要上学
We have to get up. It's a school day.
‎今天不去了
Not today.
‎今天我们就躺在床上
Today we stay in bed.
‎（艾米做完了她所需要的心脏手术）
‎（现在和她的女儿们 ‎还有孙子一起住在佛罗里达）
‎（她依旧是一名好护士）
‎字幕翻译：马特奥